Now!
All forces, charge!
Kii!
They're coming!
Don't let your guard down, everyone!
Wh-What the—
My Swordgun broke?!
Mine did, too!
Wow...
Ha ha ha.
Episode 11   What's the Point of Getting Closer?
What's with you, Reaper?
Oh, well...
I was just thinking, she's always by herself.
Gekko Princess Series
Judgment Princess
Ranran
Judgment, eh?
She's a perpetual loner who
performs her missions in silence.
The ideal Gekko soldier.
Although when she removes her mask,
she has quite a charming appearance.
Yeah, yeah!
I'm gonna go talk to her!
C'mon, mind your own business already!
Hey, Judgment!
Want to eat with us?
Another time, perhaps.
Sorry about that, Reaper-chan.
Drone Rabbit-senpai...
You know she's part of
my sixth squadron, right?
Dish Return
Leave no scraps behind! -—Bosslar
Our team specializes in covert
operations and espionage,
so she's been trained specially
in that since she joined Gekko.
Avoiding interpersonal
relationships and such.
I've asked her to at least open
up to her comrades, but...
I had no idea.
You sounded great again today!
Thanks!
Greetings!
Judgment Princess!
Hold it, Judgment!
Here!
And you'd better be there!
Princess Series Strategy Meeting
Tonight at 6
Gekko Women's Dorm
Reaper Princess's Room
Bring Pajamas
Strategy meeting?
Hey, Reaper.
Princess Series
Pajama Takoyaki Sleepover
You tricked us, damn it!
Now, now.
When I heard you were holding
a strategy meeting,
I thought it meant you were
finally taking things seriously!
And yet, you still attended in pajamas.
Shut up!
But...
When did you two get so chummy?
I wish I could tell you!
Knowing you, you set this up to get
closer to Judgment Princess, right?
But there's no way she's coming.
Unlike you, she's a solitary warrior who—
It's open! Come on in!
Fudo... why?!
H-Hey, you're...
Red Gelato?
Going for a one-man raid, huh?!
Wait a minute.
Can it...
Can it be...
Fine by me! I'll take it from here!
Wait, Beast! That's—
Ha ha ha.
It is I. Surprised?
Though I admit, your perpetual
combat readiness does impress.
Did you see through my disguise, Reaper?
First, he would never take his shoes
off in such a haphazard fashion.
And your biceps brachii
muscles were a bit too small.
Impressive.
That's the rival I know.
She really does her research.
Okay, it's ready!
Let's eat!
Hey, that's pretty tasty!
It's wonderful with cheese in, too!
I was informed that this
was a strategy meeting.
What is its actual point?
It's more like a friendly gathering.
The purpose is for all of us to get closer.
What is the point of getting closer?
Yeah, I totally get how you feel!
But don't even bother.
Reaper's pretty damned
good at getting her way.
Now that we're here,
enjoying yourself is the only option.
And you do seem to be enjoying
yourself, Beast-san.
A-Am not!
Have some, Judgment!
Is this your first time eating takoyaki?
It's very good.
Yes, it's quite delicious.
You're gonna give me a heart attack!
I'm sorry. I feel hesitant
to express myself freely.
That's no reason to retreat into a disguise!
Now, one big sleepover staple
is talking about romance!
Do you ever talk about anything else?
But being in love can inspire you in work!
The hell?
Personal Achievements on the Rise
I guess that is pretty convincing,
coming from you.
What is "being in love"?
Is being in love beneficial?
Oh, it's nothing but!
Can you describe the effects
of "being in love"?
It makes every day feel joyous,
like everything around you is shining!
This suggests that you are
currently in a state of love.
W-Well... we're not talking
about me right now.
We are. You can't escape it.
Who is it? Is it anybody I know?
I-I'm not telling!
Very well. I'll commence guessing.
This one?
There's no way it's Red, Judgment.
I wonder...
You're blushing, Reaper-san.
I-I think I turned the heater up too high.
Boy, it's hot in here!
O-Oh, I know!
I've got presents!
Here!
To celebrate our new friendship!
Then, we are friends?
Yeah, totally!
And I made one for each of you!
Why in the world would you
make this stuff, Reaper?
But of course, she is
in the handicrafts club!
Are you leaving, Judgment?
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting me today.
I never intended to get closer with you all.
I intended to leave immediately.
But I do believe that I enjoyed myself.
Yes.
Come see us again sometime, Judgment.
You bet I will!
Sh-She gave me a heart attack...
Ha ha ha!
Hey, Fudo.
Are you really Fudo?
What are you talking about, Desumi-sa—
Hey! You're breaking my face!
Desumi—
Rip
Wh-What are you doing, Desumi-san?!
I... I'm sorry, Fudo.
Love After World Domination.
You fell for my trap, heroes!
Here on this snowy mountain,
you can't even move!
Isn't the same true for you?
No way...
He's right!
Anyway, go, Gekko soldiers!
I said, go!
Mt. Takao Summit
Your coffee really is
truly exceptional, Desumi-san.
You old kidder!
The truth is, Desumi-san...
I have big news today.
At last, the book I worked so
hard on has been published!
Which Insects Would Be Strongest if They Were Giant?
A Treatise
By Fudo Aikawa
Here it is!
That's incredible!
Well done, Fudo!
To celebrate it going on sale,
I'm going to have a signing
at the bookstore tomorrow.
A signing?
Would you stop by if you
have time, Desumi-san?
Of course I'll be there!
Even if it kills me!
The
Next
Day
Which Insects Would Be Strongest if They Were Giant?
A Treatise
By Fudo Aikawa
Desumi. Desumi!
C'mon, Desumi! Don't ignore me!
You want to go to a movie after school?
I'll pass for today. I've
got a signing to go to.
A signing?
For this book?
That book looks weird!
Regardless, it's important to me!
We'll go out another time.
You're bright red, though.
Well, I wouldn't say that...
No, you're seriously red.
Are you sure you don't have a fever?
A-Actually...
Hot
I am feeling a little... dizzy...
Hey... Desumi?!
Wh-What are you doing?
Got to get... to the signing...
In your condition?!
It could kill you!
Come on, get real.
Let's get you to the nurse's office.
I did spend the whole
day on a snowy mountain,
but I was in a snow hut, at least...
That's what you do for fun?!
Nurse's Office
I sense... illness.
Sanzugawa-sensei, she's got a fever.
Oh, poor thing!
Blood Princess...
Allow me to explain!
As revealed in the previous
episode's signs,
Nurse Sanzugawa is actually
Desumi's colleague, Blood Princess!
Just leave her to me.
No... I have to get to the signing...
Thanks for taking her!
Take care, dears!
Did Sanzugawa-sensei seem weirdly
happy about this to you?
Oh, come on!
Nurse's Office
Fudo...
Which Insects Would Be Strongest if They Were Giant?
A Treatise
Now Available
Fudo Aikawa Book Signing
A chain?
How are you feeling?
Blood?
Don't worry. You're safe now.
Now, let's get you changed,
Reaper-chan.
Have to get to... book signing...
What are you doing?!
Come, now, let's wipe off that sweat.
Cut it out!
Someone as strong as you is rarely injured,
so this is the first time I've
been able to attend to you.
Now, dearie, let Mommy look after you.
Please go away!
Hey, Desumi!
About our part-time job today…
Huh? She's not here?
Desumi caught a cold.
She's probably still sleeping
in the nurse's office.
What?!
Desumi-san caught a cold?
How unusual...
That's not good.
What is it?
I left myself in Blood's care once before.
Sorry, Blood.
Can I ask for some treatment?
Oh, most certainly.
She treats anyone she
looks after like a baby!
Her motherly instincts are out of control!
I managed to escape with my life,
but Mommy almost brainwashed
me in the process!
Perhaps she succeeded?
You just called her "Mommy."
Even if she is my rival, Reaper is my friend!
I have to save her from that hell!
Do you think you can beat her?
Yeah, when she sees someone
who's sick, she loses all judgment.
We'll pretend to be sick to get close to her,
and when she lets her guard down,
we'll give her a pounding!
I haven't forgotten what you put me through.
Listen up, Mommy! I'm about
to traumatize you!
Stay safe until we get there, Reaper!
Blood... what is going on?
Now, now, dearie.
It's "Mommy," not "Blood."
Here you are, sweetie, some nice porridge.
Oh, look at you! You're chewing so good!
Is it tasty?
My sweetie little girl!
Not good...
The signing's about to start...
Oh, darling dear. Are we sleepy?
There, there. Mommy's here for nappy-time.
Now, she'll read for you from
her original picture book...
Fight!
Bosslar-kun
"Long, long ago, in a far-away land,
there was a strong, brave,
and occasionally very silly
little boy named Bosslar-kun..."
Momotaro
"The old man went to the
mountains to gather wood,
while the old woman went to
the river to do the washing..."
Mommy...
Desumi!
Desumi-san!
Keep your voices down, girls.
The baby just got to sleep.
Not good!
She's gotten pretty far along...
Are the two of you under the weather as well?
Y-Yeah, my stomach hurts...
And I have a bit of a cough!
How awful!
Let me look after you!
She fell for it!
Click!
Ow, ow...
Where are we?
Special Nurse's Office
"Special nurse's office"?
We don't have enough beds
up there, so I'll treat you here!
Nurse's Office
Th-This is... Desumi-san's...
Are you all right, Desumi-san?
You weren't answering your
phone, so I went looking...
Wh-Why is she sleeping like this?
Desumi-san...
Read it again...
R-Read... it?
Yeah... Yeah...
Then I shall.
Nurse's Office
"And in this writer's humble opinion,
the strongest insect is...
Of course, the ant!
Because the ant can lift several
times its own weight with its jaws—"
Fudo?
You're up, Desumi-san?
Why are you—
I-It's not like that, Fudo!
I was... delirious with a fever...
What? You have a fever, Desumi-san?!
That's awful!
Don't do that out of the blue!
You're making the fever worse!
S-Sorry, I wasn't thinking...
What about the signing?
You didn't slip out, did you?
Well, actually...
Fudo Aikawa Book Signing
We didn't get a single customer.
R-Really?
Does that mean I get the first autograph?
Yes, of course!
"And so, they lived happily
ever after together."
Isn't that lovely?
Goo-goo...
Mommy...
Did you hear someone reading aloud just now?
I didn't.
It's probably in your head!
Fudo Aikawa
Desumi-san...
Fudo...
Desumi-san.
Fudo.
Desumi-san!
Fudo!
Desumi-san!!
Fudo!!
Episode 12  Eternal Rivals
Next time, the final episode: "Eternal Rivals"!
See you then!